Starts with Tenacious D Tribute: a prompt generator that has to be able to round trip. The goal is round trip a prompt -> to a repo -> to a prompt. While sounding like Gandalf, using the local image generator to make the full repo presentation, including a Quine github pages describing it. 

Inspired by ascii art code, words and story as art as code. Font for VSCode, reskin it biblically?

Project Genesis: You start with 
let
there
be
light.
